希望你们准备好了
Hope to hell you boys are ready.
因为战争刚打响了
Because the war's just begun.
（忆往昔）
我是维克多·亨里克森特别探员
This is Special Agent Victor Henriksen.
我的工作是抓你回来
It's my job to bring you in.
活着更好 但不非得
Alive's a bonus, but not necessary.
给他宣读指控
Read him the charges.
持械抢劫 绑架
Armed robbery, kidnapping, and,
三起一级谋杀
three counts of first-degree murder.
我是你在这世上最不想招惹的人
I am the last person on planet Earth you wanna screw with.
这就是露比吗
So this is Ruby, huh?
未曾有幸呢
Never had the pleasure.
我来找你是因为我想帮你
I'm here because I wanna help you.
她是个恶魔 萨姆 就这么简单 好吗
She's a demon, Sam. Period. All right?
他们想要我们死 我们想要他们死
They want us dead, we want them dead.
露比 她曾是个女巫
Ruby, here, was a witch.
当然了 你那时还是人类
Of course that was when you were human.
你…
And you…
是萨姆·温彻斯特
are Sam Winchester.
小子国王
The Boy King.
萨姆本该成为大统领
Sam was supposed to be the Grand Pooh Bah,
带领军队 但是
lead the big army. But.
他并没有承担这个责任
he hasn't exactly stepped up to the plate.
崛起了新领袖
There's a new leader rising.
他不怎么喜欢你
He doesn't like you very much.
不喜欢有竞争
Doesn't want the competition.
现在外面还有几百个恶魔呢
There are a couple hundred more demons out there now.
全世界的猎人加起来
There ain't enough hunters in the world.
都不足以应付这种局面
to handle something like this.
贝拉偷了柯尔特枪
Bela stole the Colt.
真不敢相信她又胜了我们一次
Can't believe she got another one over on us.
你晚上怎么睡得着
How do you sleep at night?
裸着身在钱里打滚
Rolling naked in money.
收拾东西
Pack your crap.
我们要去找到那贱人
We're gonna go hunt the bitch down.
（如今）
（科罗拉多州 蒙纽门特）
找到了吗
Any sign of it?
没有
Nothing.
确定这是贝拉的房间吗
Sure this is Bela's room?
应该是
I'd say so.
迪恩
Dean?
亲爱的 你在吗
Sweetie, are you there?
你在哪
Where are you?
- 已经在两州之外了 - 哪里
- Two states away by now. - Where?
我们平常总会玩笑着拌嘴 我想念那样了
Where's our usual quippy banter? I miss it.
我要拿回它 贝拉 马上
I want it back, Bela. Now.
那把小手枪吗
You little pistol, you mean?
抱歉 现在不行
Sorry. I can't at the moment.
你知道你这么做会害死多少人吗
You understand how many people are gonna die if you do this?
你究竟以为我打算拿它做什么
What exactly is it that you think I plan to do with it?
拿走我们对付恶魔大军的唯一武器
Take the only weapon we have against an army of demons.
卖给出价最高者
and sell it to the highest bidder?
你对我一无所知
You know nothing about me.
我知道我要阻止你
I know I'm gonna stop you.
找都找不到我的人还撂狠话呢
Tough words for a guy who can't even find me.
我会找到你的 亲爱的
I'll find you sweetheart.
知道为什么吗
You know why?
因为对我来说 没什么事
Because I have absolutely nothing better to do…
比找到你更要紧
than to track you down.
这你就错了
That's where you're wrong.
你马上就要忙起来了
You're about to be quite occupied.
你真以为我不会采取措施防范你们吗
Did you really think I wouldn't take precautions?
手举起来
Hands in the air!
- 别动 - 跪下
- Don't move. - Down on your knees.
那贱人
That bitch.
马上趴下
On the ground. Now.
快点
Do it.
上
Go!
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特 你们有权保持沉默
Sam and Dean Winchester, you have the right to remain silent.
你们所说的一切
Anything you say.
都可以 也将被用作呈堂证供
can and will be used against you in a court of law.
你们有权找律师
You have the right to speak to an attorney…
在审讯期间有律师陪伴
and have an attorney present during any questioning.
如果你们请不起律师
If you cannot afford a lawyer,
政府会为你们指派一位
one will be appointed for you at government expense.
你们好啊
Guys.
好久没见
It's been a while.
[邪恶力量 第3季第12集]
你抓到他们了吗
So did you get them?
人都哪去了 我叫你把人都叫来的
Where's everyone? I asked for all your men.
给你派去了 跟你一起去抓人了
And you got them. They went with you on the raid.
就四个人
Four men. That's all.
那是一小时内能叫到的所有人了
Everyone I could drum up with an hour's notice.
我们是个小镇 亨里克森探员
We're a small town, Agent Henriksen.
他为什么进来的
What's he in for?
醉酒闹事
Drunk and disorderly.
钥匙
Keys.
马上
Now.
你干什么
What are you doing?
你今晚走运了 先生 你可以走了
It is your lucky night, sir. You are free to go.
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
这边
This way.
亨里克森探员 你不能随意放了我的犯人
Agent Henriksen, you can't just release my prisoners.
亨里克森探员
Agent Henriksen?
我懂
Look, I get it.
你这小镇一向风平浪静
You're Mayberry P.D.
什么
Excuse me?
如果我能选 我也不会这么做
And this isn't how I would do it if I had my choice.
但线索就是线索 我们必须快速行动
But a tip's a tip and we had to move fast.
探员 我也不是菜鸟了
Look, agent. This ain't my first rodeo.
你从未见识过这样的情况
You've never been to a rodeo like this before.
你知道我们要带来的是什么人吗
You have any idea who we're about to bring in here?
嗯 两个逃犯
Yeah, a couple of fugitives.
他们是你见过的最危险的罪犯
The most dangerous criminals you've ever laid your eyeballs on.
就像是汉尼拔·莱克特和他的蠢弟弟
Think Hannibal Lecter and his half-wit little brother.
你知道他们做什么找刺激吗
Do you know what these guys do for kicks?
挖坟 损坏尸体
Dig up graves and mutilate corpses.
他们不仅仅是杀人犯 治安官
They're not just killers, sheriff,
他们是撒旦崇拜的疯子杀人犯
they're Satan-worshipping nut-bag killers.
所以 配合我一下
So work with me here.
我会尽快带他们离开 送去重刑监狱
I'll get them out of your hair and on their way to Supermax…
你赶回家时 还来得及看《农业报告》
and you'll be home in enough time to watch the Farm Report.
一定全力配合
However we can help.
你的人
Those men of yours.
安排在各个出口处
Post them at the exits.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
- 里德 - 嗯 维克
- Reidy. - Yeah, Vic?
带进来吧
Bring them in.
我们不可能准备得更好了
Guess we're as ready as we're gonna be.
收到 就来
Got it. On our way in.
怎么都拉个脸
Why all the sourpusses?
（南茜·菲茨杰拉德 秘书）
我带你们去牢房
I'll show you to the cells.
下手轻点
Watch the merchandise.
我们不是你该怕的人 南茜
We're not the ones you should be scared of, Nancy.
迪恩 拜托
Dean, come on.
好吧
All right, all right.
坐下吗
Sit?
嗯
Yeah.
我们这次要怎么逃脱
How are we gonna Houdini out of this one?
好问题
Good question.
是我 史蒂文在吗
It's me. Is Steven in?
那叫他从会议室里出来
Well, get him out of the meeting.
（通缉 迪恩·温彻斯特 萨姆·温彻斯特）
- 格罗夫斯 - 我抓到他们了
- Groves. - I got them.
真没想到
Well, I'll be damned.
我本以为你的墓碑上会写着
I was betting on your headstone reading,
「抓不到温家兄弟」呢
"Couldn't catch the Winchester boys."
他们明早就会在重刑监狱了
Well, they'll be at Supermax by morning.
怎么去
How?
重兵把守的装甲车
Armored bus loaded with men.
装甲车 你想再让我气出溃疡来吗
A bus. What, are you trying to give me an ulcer?
听着 我们会采取一切防范
Look, we're taking every precaution.
就像上次吗
Like the last time?
还有上上次
And the time before that?
去他的 我要派直升机去
Screw that, I'm sending a chopper.
听你的
Whatever you think is best.
当然 我也去
Damn right, and I'll be on it.
不能让你再把他们丢了
Can't take you losing those boys again.
他们这几个月来一直是我的头等麻烦
They have been a primary thorn in my ass for months.
- 维克多 - 嗯
- So, Victor? - Yeah?
我到之前 眼睛不要离开他们
Glue your eyeballs to them till I get there.
有架直升机要来了
There's a chopper on its way.
嗯 我们没有停机坪
Yeah. But we don't have a helicopter pad.
那就把停车场清空
Then clear the damn parking lot.
知道我在琢磨什么吗
You know what I'm trying to decide?
我不知道 什么
I don't know, what,
壮阳药能否改善你的小问题吗
whether Cialis will help you with your little condition?
今晚吃什么晚饭
What to have for dinner tonight.
牛排还是龙虾
Steak or lobster?
不管了 海陆大餐好了
What the hell. Surf and turf.
我有很值得庆祝的事 毕竟
I got a lot to celebrate. I mean, after all,
看到你俩戴着镣铐
seeing you two in chains?
你个重口的混蛋 我们可不是那种人
You kinky son of a bitch. We don't swing that way.
真逗
Now, that's funny.
还是先别急着庆祝
You know, I wouldn't bust out the melted butter just yet.
你在银行没抓到我们
Couldn't catch us at the bank.
在监狱里没看住我们
Couldn't keep us in that jail.
是啊 我搞砸了
You're right. Screwed up.
我低估了你们 我没想到你们那么聪明
I underestimated you. I didn't count on you being that smart.
但我现在准备好了
But now I'm ready.
嗯 准备好再弄丢我们吗
Yeah. Ready to lose us again?
准备好了法庭命令
Ready like a court order.
在庭审前都把你们扣在内华达州的重刑监狱里
to keep you in a super-maximum prison in Nevada till trial.
准备好了把你们隔离在隔音无窗的小牢房里
Ready like isolation in a soundproof, windowless cell so small.
私下里跟你说 那可能违宪了
that between you and me, probably unconstitutional.
这准备得如何
How's that for ready?
好好看看萨姆吧
Take a good look at Sam.
你俩再别想相见了
You two will never see each other again.
你自鸣得意的笑容呢 迪恩
Where's that smug smile, Dean?
我想看看
I wanna see it.
你抓错人了
You got the wrong guys.
嗯 我忘了
Yeah. I forgot.
你们是打怪的
You fight monsters.
抱歉 迪恩 其实
Sorry, Dean. Truth is.
是你们爸爸拿魔鬼论调给你们洗了脑
your daddy brainwashed you with all that devil talk.
而且肯定还摸过你们不该摸的地方
and no doubt touched you in a bad place.
就是这样 这才是真相
That's all. That's reality.
你闭嘴吧
Why don't you shut your mouth?
知道吗 生活糟心 自备头盔
But guess what? Life sucks, get a helmet.
因为每个人都有伤心事
Because everybody's got a sob story.
但不是每个人都会变成杀人犯
But not everybody becomes a killer.
现在我又少了两个
And now I have two less.
需要担心的杀人犯
to worry about.
海陆大餐时间到
It's surf-and-turf time.
史蒂文
Steven.
先生们
Gentlemen.
- 这是什么 - 没办法
- What's all this? - What can I say?
联调局没有发明官僚主义 但我们完善了它
The FBI didn't invent bureaucracy, we perfected it.
你要我现在把这些都办妥吗
You want me to do all this now?
抱歉 是的 维克多
Sorry. Now, Victor.
我要去好好看看我们的逃犯
I'm gonna go take a good long gander at our fugitives.
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特
Sam and Dean Winchester.
我是史蒂文·格罗夫斯副局长
I'm Deputy Director Steven Groves.
真是荣幸
This is a pleasure.
很高兴我们中有一个人那么想
Well, glad one of us feels that way.
我等你们
I've been waiting a long time.
自己现身等了好久
for you two to come out of the woodwork.
抱歉 我得先走了
Sorry, I've gotta cut this short.
今晚会很漫长了 两位
It's gonna be a long night, fellas.
那怎么回事
What the hell was that?
- 放下枪 - 等等
- All right. Put the gun down. - Wait. Okay. Wait.
- 他打了他 - 我没打他
- He shot him. - I didn't shoot him.
- 放下 - 我没打谁
- Down. - I didn't shoot anyone.
- 他打了我 - 马上跪下
- He shot me. - Get on your knees now.
好好 别开枪 拜托
Okay, okay. Okay, don't shoot, please.
来 给
Look, here. Here.
好了
Okay. Look.
我们没开枪 你去看尸体
We didn't shoot him. Check the body.
没有血迹 我们没杀他
There's no blood. We did not kill him.
去看看他
Go ahead. Check him.
维克 没有子弹伤
Vic, there's no bullet wound.
他可能都死几个月了
He's probably been dead for months.
你们对他做了什么
What did you do to him?
我们什么都没做
We didn't do anything.
交待 不然我开枪了
Talk or I shoot.
你不会相信我们的
You won't believe us.
他被附身了
He was possessed.
附身了 好啊
Possessed. Right.
启动直升机 我们马上带他们走
Fire up the chopper, we're taking them out of here now.
嗯 就这么干
Yeah, do that.
比尔
Bill.
比尔 你在吗
Bill, you there?
他们死了
They're dead.
他们好像都死了
I think they're all dead.
那怎么回事 里德
What the hell was that? Reidy?
里德
Reidy?
里德 外面怎么回事 里德
Reidy? What is going on out there? Reidy?
那怎么回事 回复
What the hell was that? Come in.
说话啊
Talk to me.
回复
Come in.
说话啊 里德
Talk to me, Reidy.
- 喂 - 我的人
- Hello? - My men.
- 亨里克森探员 - 喂
- Agent Henriksen? - Hello?
外面发生了什么事
What the hell's happening out there?
线路不通 所有电话都断线了
I can't get a line. All the phones are out.
亨里克森 我四个手下呢
Henriksen! Four of my men.
网络 我的手机
The Internet, I… My cell.
都断线了 这怎么可能
It's all dead. How can it all be dead?
那绝不是好事
That can't be good.
天啊
My God.
不不 没事的
No, no. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
我们走 我们这就走
We're gonna go. We're gonna go right now.
- 走 - 没人可以离开
- Let's go. - Nobody's going anywhere.
所有人冷静
Everybody calm down.
你的搭档在外面 我的手下也…
Your partner is out there. My men are out…
我知道
I know.
我们出去 也是找死
We go out there, we're asking to die too.
- 你还不懂吗 - 什么
- Don't you get it? - What?
他们在外面 想进来
They're out there and they're coming in here.
这是包围
This is a siege.
所以你现在
So this might be a good time.
应该锁好门窗
for you to lock the doors and the windows.
喘口气 像个理智的
take a breath, and maybe deal with this.
专业人士那样应对这个局面
like train professionals with some sense in their heads.
你还好吗
You okay?
我猜也是
I wouldn't think so.
南茜 是吗
Nancy, right?
我会帮你撑过去的 我保证
I'm gonna get you through this, you got my word.
知道了吗
You got that?
好了 别那么怂
All right, don't be such a wuss.
怎么打算的
What's the plan?
杀了警局所有人 把你们救出去吗
Kill everyone in the station and bust you two out?
你说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
我说的是你们的疯子朋友
I'm talking about your psycho friends,
我说的是他们的血洗
I'm talking about a bloodbath.
好吧 我保证
Okay, I promise you:
不管外面是谁 他们不是来帮我们的
Whoever's out there is not here to help us.
你得相信我们
Look, you gotta believe us.
这里的人都身陷险境
Everyone here is in terrible danger.
用你说
You think?
你放我们出去 让我们救你吧
Why don't you let us out of here so we can save your asses?
是什么要来
From what?
你要说「恶魔」吗
You gonna say "demons"?
你敢说「恶魔」
Don't you dare say "demons."
我告诉你们 你们该更怕我
Let me tell you something. You should be a lot more scared of me.
肩膀怎么样了
How's the shoulder?
好极了
It's awesome.
我死不了
I'll live.
如果我们能活着出去的话
You know, if we get out of here alive.
你有计划吗
So you got a plan?
拜托 我们需要你帮忙
Please. Please, we need your help.
是南茜 是吗
It's Nancy? Nancy, right?
南茜 我哥哥被打中了
Nancy, my brother's been shot.
他在严重流血
He's bleeding really bad.
你能不能给我们找条毛巾来
Do you think maybe you could get us a towel?
拜托 就一条干净毛巾
Please, just one clean towel?
看着我们 我们不是坏人 我发誓
Look. Look at us. We're not the bad guys. I swear.
尝试可嘉
Nice try.
谢谢
Thank you.
没事的
It's okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
Thanks.
放开她
Let her go! Let her go!
好
Okay.
有病
Freak.
你没事吧 南茜
You okay, Nance?
再敢耍花招 我就开枪
Try something again, get shot.
- 而且不会打胳膊了 - 好
- And not in the arm. - Okay.
你那是干什么
What the hell was that?
我们在这里就是活靶子
We're like sitting ducks in here.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
这些该死的警察给我们点吃的能死啊
Would it kill these cops to bring us a snack?
你觉得外面有多少
How many you figure are out there?
我不知道
I don't know.
不管他们有多少 他们能附身任何人
However many they are, they could be possessing anyone.
任何人都能直接走进来
Anyone could just walk right in.
还挺疯狂的 是吧
It's kind of wild, right?
他们直冲我们来了
I mean it's like, they're coming right for us.
这可是前所未有
Never done that before.
就好像我们被悬赏了
It's like we got a contract on us.
你觉得是因为我们太厉害了吗
You think it's because we're so awesome?
我觉得是因为我们太厉害了
I think it's because we're so awesome.
好啊 治安官
Well, howdy there, sheriff.
治安官
Sheriff?
该走了 小子们
It's time to go, boys.
知道吗
You know what?
我们在这里挺好 但谢谢了
We're just comfy right here, but thank you.
你在干什么
What do you think you're doing?
我不要坐在这里等死
I'm not just gonna sit around here and wait to die.
我们要试试逃跑
We're gonna make a run for it.
这里更安全
It's safer here.
博尔德有个特警队
There's a SWAT facility in Boulder.
我们哪都不去
We're not going anywhere.
怎么不了
The hell we're not.
别过来
Stay back.
萨姆 快点
Sam, hurry up.
太迟了
It's too late.
我已经召唤他们了 他们在赶来了
I already called them. They're already coming.
他…死了吗
Is he…? Is he dead?
亨里克森
Henriksen.
那是你吗
Is that you in there?
我…
I, uh…
我打死了治安官
I shot the sheriff.
但你没打死副局长
But you didn't shoot the deputy.
五分钟前 我还好好的 然后
Five minutes ago I was fine and then…
我猜猜
Let me guess.
一股可怕的黑烟
Some nasty black smoke…
钻进了你的喉咙里
jammed itself down your throat?
你被附身了
You were possessed.
附身 真附身吗
Possessed, like possessed.
那就是附身的感觉 你现在知道了
That's what it feels like. Now you know.
我真该跟你说个大大的「我早说了」
I owe you the biggest I-told-you-so ever.
阿米奇警官
Officer Amici.
钥匙
Keys.
好
All right.
那我们要怎么活下来
So how do we survive?
不错 但没什么用的
Well, that's nice. It's not gonna do much good.
我们有一个军火库呢
We got an arsenal here.
你不能拿BB枪打熊
You don't poke a bear with a BB gun.
那只会惹怒它
It's just gonna make him mad.
你需要什么
What do you need?
盐
Salt.
很多盐
Lots and lots of salt.
盐吗
Salt?
这里还有回声啊
Is there an echo in here?
仓库里有除冰盐
There's road salt in the storeroom.
很好
Perfect.
很好 在所有窗口和门口撒盐
Perfect. We need salt at every window and every door.
你还好吗 南茜
How you holding up, Nancy?
还好
Okay.
我小时候
When I was little,
从教堂回到家后 会聊起魔鬼
I would come home from church and talk about the devil.
我父母会叫我别那么当真
My parents would tell me to stop being so literal.
这下我让他们知道了
I guess I showed them, huh?
应该可以了
That should hold.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Sure.
我的车呢
Where's my car?
- 在后面的扣押车场 - 好
- Impound lot out back. - Okay.
等等
Wait.
你不是要出去吧
You're not going out there?
嗯 我得从后备箱里拿点东西来
Yeah, I gotta get something out of my trunk.
（蒙纽门特警局车辆扣押场）
他们来了
They're coming!
快
Hurry!
大家都还好吗
Everybody okay?
什么叫「还好」
Define "okay."
好吧 大家都戴上这个
Right, everybody needs to put these on.
能防止你被附身
It'll keep you from being possessed.
给
Here you go.
你和萨姆呢
What about you and Sam?
明智
Smart.
你们文多久了
How long have you had those?
不够久
Not long enough.
（马文·多德 治安官）
那是珍娜·鲁布纳
That's Jenna Rubner.
那不是珍娜了
That's not Jenna anymore.
那些恶魔黑烟就进入了他们吗
That's where all that black demon smoke went?
看来是的
Looks like.
装了盐弹的猎枪
Shotgun shells full of salt.
好用就行
Whatever works.
用调味料打怪
Fighting off monsters with condiments.
原来恶魔是真的
So turns out demons are real.
对了 鬼魂也是真的
FYI, ghosts are real too.
还有狼人 吸血鬼
So are werewolves, vampires…
魔童 吃人的邪恶小丑
changelings, evil clowns that eat people.
那好吧
Okay, then.
如果能让你好受点 大脚怪是骗人的
If it makes you feel better, Bigfoot's a hoax.
没好受点
It doesn't.
有多少恶魔
How many demons?
总数吗
Total?
不知道 很多
No clue. A lot.
你知道我的工作是什么吗
You know what my job is?
除了把好人关起来吗
You mean, besides locking up the good guys?
不知道
No, I have no idea.
我的工作很无趣
My job is boring.
很让人挫败
It's frustrating.
为了一个突破要忙三年
You work three years for one break…
然后你或许能救下几个人 或许吧
and then maybe you can save a few people. Maybe.
那就是你的回报
That's the payoff.
为了抓几个人 忙活了15年
Been busting my ass for 15 years to nail a handful of guys…
而与此同时 角落里却有这么可怕的东西
and all this while, there was something off in the corner so big.
是的
So, yeah,
给我定制一个「浪费人生」的杯子吧
sign me up for that big frosty mug of wasting my damn life.
你又不知道
You didn't know.
我现在知道了
Well, now I do.
外面的东西
What's out there?
你们能打败他们吗
Can you guys beat it?
你们能赢吗
Can you win?
老实说 我觉得世界会走向血腥的末日
Honestly, I think the world's gonna end bloody.
但那不代表我们就该放弃抵抗
But that doesn't mean we shouldn't fight.
我们还有选择
We do have choices.
我选择英勇就义
I choose to go down swinging.
而且 你也没有家 只有你弟弟
Plus, you got nothing to go home to but your brother.
对
Yeah.
你呢 你有模板般的美好生活吗
What about you, you rocking the white-picket fence?
没有 空荡荡的公寓 一堆愤怒前妻
No. Empty apartment, string of angry ex-wives.
我跟你一样
I'm right where you are.
想想看啊
Imagine that.
我们怎么杀她
How do we kill her?
我们不杀她
We don't.
- 她是恶魔 - 她是来帮忙的
- She's a demon. - She's here to help us.
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
你不放我出去吗
Are you gonna let me out?
人们还说骑士精神已死呢
And they say chivalry's dead.
谁有薄荷糖吗
Does anyone have a breath mint?
我一路杀进来时
Some guts splattered in my mouth,
嘴里溅进了点肠子
while I was killing my way in here.
外面有多少
How many are out there?
至少30个 还只是目前
Thirty at least. That's so far.
好啊 30个
Good. Thirty.
30个冲我们来的杀手
Thirty hit men all gunning for us.
谁派他们来的
Who sent them?
你没告诉迪恩吗
You didn't tell Dean?
我真意外
I'm surprised.
告诉我什么
Tell me what?
来了个新红人 很有感召力
There's a big new up-and-comer. A real pied piper.
他是谁
Who is he?
不是他
Not he.
是她
Her.
她叫莉莉丝
Her name is Lilith.
莉莉丝
Lilith?
她真的很想把萨姆的内脏插在棍子上
And she really, really wants Sam's intestines on a stick.
她大概是把他视为竞争对手
Guess she sees him as competition.
你知道吗
You knew about this?
天啊 萨姆 还有什么我该知道的事吗
Well, jeez, Sam. Is there anything else I should know?
你俩回头再吵吧
How about the two of you talk about this later?
我们需要柯尔特枪
We'll need the Colt.
柯尔特枪呢
Where's the Colt?
被偷了
It got stolen.
对不起 我肯定是耳朵里进血了
I'm sorry, I must have blood in my ear.
我以为我听到你说
I thought I just heard you say.
你蠢到让人从你粗笨的手里
that you were stupid enough to let the Colt get grabbed out of.
抢走了柯尔特枪
your thick, clumsy, idiotic hands.
太好了
Fantastic.
这真是太好了
This is just peachy.
- 露比 - 闭嘴
- Ruby… - Shut up.
好吧
Fine.
既然我看不出还有别的办法
Since I don't see that there's any other option,
我还有个能救你们活着离开的办法
there's one other way I know how to get you out of here alive.
什么办法
What's that?
我知道个咒语
I know a spell.
能消灭一英里内
It'll vaporize every demon…
所有的恶魔
in a one-mile radius.
包括我自己
Myself included.
所以你弄丢了柯尔特枪 而我要为此而死
So you let the Colt out of your sight and now I have to die.
下次 要更小心点
So next time, be more careful.
这个遗愿如何
How's that for a dying wish?
好吧 我们需要做什么
Okay. What do we need to do?
你什么都做不了
You can't do anything.
这个咒语很特定
This spell is very specific.
需要一个有美德的人
It calls for a person of virtue.
我有美德
I got virtue.
想得美
Nice try.
你不是处子
You're not a virgin.
不会有人是处子的
Nobody's a virgin.
不 不可能
No. No way.
你开玩笑吧 你…
You're kidding me. You're…
怎么了 这是个选择 好吗
What? It's a choice, okay?
怎么 你…你从未…
What, so you…? You never…?
一次都没有吗
Not even once?
甚至都没…
I mean, not even…?
这个咒语
So the spell.
需要我做什么
What can I do?
你可以别动
You can hold still…
让我把你的心从胸口挖出来
while I cut your heart out of your chest.
- 什么 - 你疯了吗
- What? - What are you crazy?
我提出了一个办法
I'm offering a solution.
你要杀人
You're offering to kill somebody.
你以为等恶魔冲进来后
And what do you think's gonna happen to this girl.
这姑娘又会怎样
when the demons get in?
- 我们会保护她的 - 不好意思
- We're gonna protect her. That's what. - Excuse me.
真高尚
Very noble.
- 不好意思 - 你们都会死的
- Excuse me? - You're all gonna die.
- 这是唯一的办法 - 嗯嗯
- This is the only way. - Yeah, yeah,
- 我们绝不可能 - 相信我
- there's no way… - Trust me.
- 让你… - 大家能不能闭嘴
- that you're gonna prove… - Will everybody please shut up.
外面那些人
All the people out there…
这能救他们吗
will it save them?
能把他们体内的恶魔炸飞
It'll blow the demons out of their bodies.
所以如果他们的身体还完好 那就没问题
So if their bodies are okay, yeah.
- 那我做 - 不
- I'll do it. - No. No.
- 绝对不行 - 你不用这么做
- Hell, no. - You don't need to do this.
我的朋友都在外面
All my friends are out there.
我们不会牺牲任何人
We don't sacrifice people.
我们那么做 也不比他们强了
We do that, we're no better than them.
我们没有选择
We don't have a choice.
- 你的选择不叫选择 - 萨姆
- Yeah. Well, your choice is not a choice. - Sam.
你知道我是对的
You know I'm right.
萨姆
Sam?
这是怎么了 萨姆 说啊
What the hell is going on? Sam, tell her.
这是我的决定
It's my decision.
- 说得好 小妹子 - 住口
- Damn straight, cherry pie. - Stop.
住口
Stop.
没人要杀处女
Nobody kill any virgins.
萨姆 我需要跟你谈谈
Sam, I need to talk to you.
拜托告诉我你不是在考虑这个
Please tell me you're not actually considering this.
摁住一个女孩 挖出她的心
Talking about holding down a gril and cutting out her heart.
外面还有30个人呢 迪恩
And we're also talking about 30 people out there, Dean.
无辜者
Innocent people…
他们都会死 这里的每个人也都会死
who are all gonna die, along with everyone in here.
那我们也不能放弃一切规则
It doesn't mean that we throw away the rule book.
不再做人了
and stop acting like humans.
我不能让那个恶魔
I'm not gonna let that demon.
杀一个善良可爱无辜的女孩
kill some nice, sweet, innocent girl…
连床都没上过的女孩
who hasn't even been laid.
如果你要这样赢得战争 那我不想赢了
I mean, look, if that's how you win wars, then I don't wanna win.
那怎么办
Then what?
我们怎么办 迪恩
What do we do, Dean?
我有个计划
I got a plan.
或许不是好计划
I'm not saying it's a good one,
甚至未必能成功
I'm not even saying that it'll work…
但绝对好过杀个处女
but it sure as hell beats killing a virgin.
好吧 什么计划
Okay, so, what's the plan?
打开大门 放他们进来
Open the doors. Let them all in.
然后我们战斗
And we fight.
- 设备好用吗 - 嗯
- Get the equipment to work? - Yeah.
怎么样
So?
这简直疯了
So this is insane.
这话说得太轻了
You win understatement of the year.
我明白
Look, I get it.
- 你觉得… - 不是觉得 我确定
- You think… - I don't think. I know.
这不会成功的
It's not gonna work.
再见了 小子们
So long, boys.
你就这么走了吗
So you're just gonna leave?
我都准备自杀来帮你赢了
I was gonna kill myself to help you win.
我才不要站在这里 看你们输
I'm not gonna stand here and watch you lose.
而且我很失望
And I'm disappointed.
因为我尽力了
Because I tried.
我真尽力了
I really did.
但显然 我赌错了人
But clearly, I bet on the wrong horse.
可以放我出去吗
Do you mind letting me out?
我要离开了
I'm leaving.
谁要阻止我吗
Who wants to stop me?
都好了吗
All set?
嗯
Yeah.
准备好了
Ready.
我们来吧
Let's do this.
希望这好用
God, I hope this works.
走走
Go, go, go!
等这事结束 我要敞开了做爱
When this is over, I'm gonna have so much sex.
但不是跟你
But not with you.
我们快行动吧
We better move.
亨里克森 现在
Henriksen, now!
我得上报了
I better call it in.
真是个精彩的我不能讲的故事
Hell of a story I won't be telling.
那你打算怎么跟他们讲
So, what are you gonna tell them?
我能在接下来
The least ridiculous lie.
五小时里想出最不荒唐的谎言
I can come up with in the next five minutes.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
不是想给你压力
Not to pressure you or anything but,
但你打算怎么处置我们
what're you planning to do about us?
我要杀了你们
I'm gonna kill you.
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特
Sam and Dean Winchester.
在直升机起火时也在机上
were in the chopper when it caught on fire.
烧得什么都不剩了
Nothing's left.
甚至无法靠牙科记录确认他们的身份
Can't even identify them with dental records.
安息吧 两位
Rest in peace, guys.
快走吧
Now get out of here.
嗯
Yeah.
你好
Hi there.
不好意思 我在找两个男人 一对兄弟
Excuse me, I'm looking for two boys. They're brothers.
一个很高 一个很帅
One's really tall and one's really cute?
你叫什么 亲爱的
What's your name, sweetie?
莉莉丝
Lilith.
看新闻
Turn on the news.
社区仍因几小时前发生的惨剧
The community is still reeling from the tragedy…
而悲痛不已
that happened just a few hours ago.
当局认为是煤气总管破裂
Authorities believe a gas main ruptured,
导致了巨大的爆炸
causing the massive explosion.
将警局炸毁
that ripped apart the police station.
并夺走了里面所有人的生命
and claimed the lives of everyone inside.
死者包括至少六名警官和员工
Among the deceased, at least six police officers and staff,
包括 马文·多德治安官 菲尔·阿米奇警官
including Sheriff Melvin Dodd, Deputy Phil Amici,
秘书南茜·菲茨杰拉德
secretary Nancy Fitzgerald,
还有三名联调局探员 史蒂文·格罗夫斯
as well as three FBI agents identified as Steven Groves,
凯文·里德和维克多·亨里克森
Calvin Reidy and Victor Henriksen.
两名在押逃犯也丧命了
Two fugitives in custody were also killed.
我们将继续在现场跟进报道
We'll continue to follow the story here at the scene,
但现在 回到你那里 吉姆
but for now, back to you, Jim.
肯定是我们刚走就发生了
Must've happened right after we left.
考虑到爆炸的强度
Considering the size of the blast…
我敢说是莉莉丝
smart money's on Lilith.
这是什么
What's in these?
能保护你们的东西
Something that'll protect you.
让莉莉丝找不到你们 至少暂时吧
Throw Lilith off your trail. For the time being, at least.
- 谢谢 - 别谢我
- Thanks. - Don't thank me.
莉莉丝杀了所有人
Lilith killed everyone.
她屠杀了你的宝贝处女
She slaughtered your precious little virgin.
还有半打其他人
plus a half a dozen other people.
你讲了一大顿战争中的人道主义
So after your big speech about humanity and war,
你的计划却是害死了人的那个
turns out your plan was the one with the body count.
你们知道怎么打仗吗
Do you know how to fight a battle?
先下手为强 绝不留活口
You strike fast and you don't leave any survivors,
以免有人跑去向上司打报告
so no one can go running to tell the boss.
下次 我们按我的计划来
So next time, we go with my plan.